Guide to the Organization of Staff Analysts Records WAG.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Unprocessed Materials, 1980-2005
  - Rule 5.4.2., 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - 6.1.9. Letters to Agencies - ASA List, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Letters to Agencies - ASA List, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Letters to Agencies - ASA List (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Letters to Agencies - ASA List (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - ASA List, 2001-2005 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - ASA List - Out-Of-Title Grievances, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - ASA List - General Letters to Members, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - ASA List - Letters to the "Chief", 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Sheila's Issues - Kalish and Schnieder (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Department of Citywide Administrative Services (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Department of Citywide Administrative Services (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - ASA Promotion #0509, 2/2001 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - ASA Certifications - Agency - 08/09/10/11/12/13/15/19/25/30/32/41, 10/23/2001-10/24/2005 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - ASA Certifications - Agency - 056/57/68/69/71/072/94, 10/23/2001-10/24/2005 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - ASA Certifications - Agency - 125/126/127/130/131/133/156/214/256/261, 10/23/2001-10/24/2005 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - ASA Certifications - Agency - 781/801/806/810/816-17/826/827/829, 10/23/2001-10/24/2005 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - ASA Certifications - Agency - 836/841/846/850/858, 10/23/2001-10/24/2005 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - ASA Certifications - Agency - 860/866/868/902/993/996/998, 10/23/2001-10/24/2005 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - ASA Certifications (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - ASA Certifications (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - ASA Certifications (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - ASA Certifications (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - ASA Certifications (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - ASA List - Statistics, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Ballots and referendums on union policies, 1993-2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - OSA WF, Comptroller's Report Synopsis, October 1998 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - OSA WF Benefits, December 1990 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Special Leave of Absence Coverage, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Metrocard (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation(HHC); Segundo Ruiz Belvis policy and procedure, October 1, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - HHC; No smoking policy, November 6, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - HHC; Morrisania Policy and Procedure, February 1, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - HCC; EEO Procedure #20-32, April 11, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - HHC; East New York Policy and Procedure (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - HHC; Coney Island hospital lease, June 1996 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - HHC; chapter 68, procedure 20-55, October 18, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - HHC Campaigns, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - HHC; Annual leave acruals, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Constitution, ballots; OLD, OSART, OSA; amendements, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - BOE; smoking regulations, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - BOE; payroll inquiry forms (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - BOE; original union members, March 20, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - BOE; excessing of administrative personnel, January 1990 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education; email benefits, July 2007 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - A guide for auditing local union financial records, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - NYCAPS, January 2006 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Contracts; DOH MH; pandemic fly budget, November 2006 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Contract FOIl request, May 2007 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Goodwill, 7/1/2006-6/30/2009 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - HRA contract renewal, May 2006 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - City contract renewal agreement, 12/1/2002-11/30/2005 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Contract modification agreement, 7/1/2006-6/20/2009 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - PD contract, 5/2002 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Computer specialist exam announcement, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Exams; S.A. list #3021; Appointments, 5/1996 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Exams; S.A. list #3021; Appointments/Eligibility, 3/26/1997-4/1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Exams; S.A. list #3021; Eligibility listing, 7/1/1998 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Exams; S.A. #3021; Eligibility and appointments/declines, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Exams; S.A. #3021; HRA pool, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Exams; S.A. lists of 3021, 7/1998-8/1998; 3/26/1998; 3/13/1998 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Exams; staff analyst #3021; Special list of appeals won, 10/1998-8/1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 8021; training and appeals; forms, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Exams; #8021; forms and letters, 4/1999 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Numeric list S.A. 4199, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Exams; #8021; Staff Analyst exam, 4/1999 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Exams; S.A. list #8021; Notice of Examination (NOE), 4/7/1999 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Exams; S.A. #8021; Eligibles appointed list, 4/2001 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Exams; S.A. #8021 list, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Exams; S.A. #8021, 4/1999 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Exams; S.A. #8021, 11/1999 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Trainee list #2165, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Trainee list of #2165, 3/3/1993-3/23/1993; 7/20/1994 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Exams; protest; article, 3/4/1994 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration; Board of Certification, July 12, 2004-December 13, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration; Board of Certification, January 4, 2005-June 22, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Ballots; contract question between OSA and NYC, September 12, 2001-July 21, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Election ballots, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Administrative WSA Pools #4540, 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Staff Analyst List; Alpha, 12/15/1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Exams; Staff Analyst List; appeals, numerical, severance, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Exams; Staff Analyst List; appeals, numerical, severance, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Exams; S.A. List #3021; Mayor's office; refusal to appoint, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Exams; S.A. List #3021; alpha list, December 15, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - S.A. UST #3021; alpha, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - S.A. Lists #3021; Alpha, 1/7/1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - S.A. List; numerical, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - S.A. List #3021; numeric, 1/7/1994 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Exams; #3021; E & E; alpha, numeric, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Exams; #3021; notice of exam, 6/1993 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - S.A Lists; OSA (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Exams; Staff Analyst #3021; HRA Pool, 4/1995 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Exams; #3021, Moving of exams, 4/1995 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Exams; Staff Analyst #3021; HRA SA response, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Exams; Staff Analyst #3021; Moving of exams, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Exams; lists, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Office of Labor Relations; renovations, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Retirement considerations by Paul Mouchard, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Retirement flyers, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Retirement package (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Quality of Work, 7/1/1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Rallies; flyers, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Lobbying law, 5/24/1994 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Management Benefit fund; information and forms, 8/1992 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Membership meetings, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 8/25/1995 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Municipal Labor Committee; Mental health vendor, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 5/2000 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - New York Labor History, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Overtime; weekly overtime work authorization form, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Phone Mate, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Processing Fees on PMS, 11/1997 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Public Relations Firm; rick Laughren; Consulting, Inc, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Exams; Administrative S.A.; appeals and lists, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Exams; Administrative S.A. #4540; papers, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Staff Analyst #3021, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Provisional lists; HRA, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Administrative HRA list; title, date, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Lists; Agencies; HRA administration; ASA/SA, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Lists; HRA provisional, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Lists; titles; provisional and permanent adminstration; ASA SA, 8/10/1989 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Lists; HRA; total staff, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - City-wide provisional lists; all types, 2/1996 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - City-wide provisional lists; ASA and SA, 10/23/1989 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Lists; agenicies; administration; DGS SA/ASA, 6/1989 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Lists; agencies; DJJ Analysts, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Lists; agencies; DOS analysts, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - OSA members lists; dues, 10/20/2006 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Lists; NYCHA; administration; ASA/SA, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - City-wide lists; ASA/SA, 12/21/1989 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - City-wide lists; addresses; analysts, 7/8/1991 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - City-wide lists; staff analysts, 10/21/1988 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - City-wide lists; associate staff analyst, 10/21/1988 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Overtime, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Overtime cap, 11/16/2006 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Work experience program; vigil, 9/1998 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Work experience program; unions, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Work experience program; newsprint, 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - No smoking policy; correspondence, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Smoking pollution procedure #91-2; control policy, 1993-1995 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Smoke Free Air Act, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Snow Day, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Strike plans; NYC, 6/1992 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Summer hours, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - SUPPORT: staff employee handbook, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Taxes withholding, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Training sourcebook; NYC, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Transfers; request for transfer, 3/3/1988 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Transfers; in/out agencies, leave credits, 1993;2007 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Turkey Day, 11/9/1990 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - 'Underfunding Urban America;' NYC council, 8/29/2004 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Department of Labor; employment/training administratiion, 6/1995 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Work Experience Program; conference, 11/15/1997 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Work Experience Program; conference, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Cornell University; labor relations studies, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Computer Booklets (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - The Charter Review, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Charter commission for Staten Island, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Work Experience Program; pre-conference bills; meals, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Black History Month, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Department of Business Services (DBS), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Chapters; HPD, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - New York City Housing Authority (NYCHA), 1991 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - New York City Police Department, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - HRA chapter meetings, 12/1991 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Driver improvement program, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Driver improvement program, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Basic Health Insurance benefits program, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Health benefits program description, undated (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Health plans; GHI, professional evaluation, medical group, drugs, benefits, 1998;2000 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Health plans; general, 9/2000 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - HIP, EBO; medical spend conversion (EBP), 2000 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - HIP; health plan booklet, undated (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Health plans; employee benefits program (inclusing COBRA), 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Deferred compensation, 1/2002 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Exams #5021; Training development specialist (TDS), 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - TDS list and pool; #5021, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - The Fair Tax Guide; booklets, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - FICA refunds, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Fire alarm dispatchers, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Flood, 9/2004-4/2006 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association; membership directory, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Expedited arbitration procedure, undated (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - LEAP; Queens College, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Labor News; clippings, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Wage Deferral, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - City Council; privatization, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - City Council; Ken Fisher, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - City Council; Sal Albanese, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - City Council; Introduction 232A, Smoking Bill, undated (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - Internet, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - Investment, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC); meeting, October 29, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 2009 Health Benefits Agreement between NYC and the MLC (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - MLC; Welfare funds, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - M.L.C.; meetings, December 12, 2000-February 13, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - M.L.C; meetings, December 14, 2004-September 14, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - M.L.C.; meetings, April 19, 2007-February 3, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - City contracts, July 2002 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - City contracts, 3/31/2003 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - City contracts, 7/16/2003 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - City contracts, 10/13/2005-7/13/2006 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - City contracts, 7/1/2006-6/30/2009 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - City contracts, 7/1/2006-6/30/2009 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - City contracts, 7/1/2006-6/30/2009 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - City contracts, 5/10/2007 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - City contracts, 5/2006 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - City contracts, 8/2006-12/2006 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - City contracts, 7/2002 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Back to work contract employment and training services, 7/1/2006-6/30/2009 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Business logic; DCAS-DMSS; contract agreement, 3/2005 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Concera Corp., 12/1/1999-11/30/2005 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Curtis and Associates, 12/1/1999-11/30/2002 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Curtis and Associates, 12/1/1999-11/30/2005 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - DOHMH Contract, 4/1/2006-3/31/2009 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - DOHMH contract and budget, 11/2006 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68, Box 69)